Guide to the Kim Phillips-Fein Research Files TAM.730
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Kim Phillips-Fein Research Files
1933-2008
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Phillips-Fein, Kim
TAM.730
9.5 linear feet in 9 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
Kim Phillips-Fein is a professor at New York University and author of the books, Invisible Hands: The Businessmen's Crusade Against the New Deal (2009) and Fear City (2017). She also wrote essays that have appeared in The Nation, The Atlantic, the Journal of American History, and The Baffler, among other publications. She is a Distinguished Lecturer for the Organization of American Historians (2017 – 2020). The papers in this collection are research materials used by Phillips-Fein to write her book, Invisible Hands: The Businessmen's Crusade Against the New Deal. They include copies of scholarly articles, newspaper clippings, business newsletters, and union pamphlets. Most significant are handwritten research notes and early drafts of Invisible Hands.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were recieved from the donor.
Biographical Note
Kim Phillips-Fein teaches American history at New York University, where she is an associate professor in the Gallatin School of Individualized Study. She is the author of the books Invisible Hands: The Businessmen's Crusade Against the New Deal (2009) and Fear City (2017), and acts as a Distinguished Lecturer for the Organization of American Historians (2017 - 2020). She also wrote essays that have appeared in The Nation, The Atlantic, the Journal of American History, and The Baffler, among other publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Kim Phillips-Fein, 2017. The accession number associated with this gift is 2017.057.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of research materials collected and used by Kim Phillips-Fein in the course of researching and writing her book Invisible Hands: The Businessmen's Crusade Against the New Deal. Materials include photocopies of scholarly articles, newspaper clippings, business newsletters, and union pamphlets held in archival collections at other archival and special collections repositories documenting various aspects of conservatism, labor strikes, and labor unions in the early and mid-20th century. Most significant are handwritten research notes and early drafts of Invisible Hands.
Business and politics.; Economics -- United States.; United States -- Politics and government -- 20th century.; United States -- Politics and government; Conservatism; Small business -- United States.; Political economy; Actors -- Labor unions -- United States.; Labor unions -- United States.
- Rainfair, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Liberty League, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Irenee du Pont, 1934-1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Pierre du Pont, 1936; 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Coca Cola Washington, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Defective Reports Kohler cont., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Steel Strike, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Kohler Files, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Other Kohler, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Harvard Business Review, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Harvard Business Review, 1944-1945; 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NLRB Korber, Mats, and Terminal, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Israel, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Tom Frank and His Critics, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 20th Century Political History, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Late 19th Century Economic History, 1955; 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Jacksonianism Economy, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Gilded Age, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 1960s History, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- George Koether Letters, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Ingebretsen Papers, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- War 141, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Legal Foundation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Jesse Helms Papers, 1955-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Jesse Helms Center, 1963-1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- J. Howard Pew Papers, 1944-1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Labor Legislation - National Association of Manufacturers (NAM), 1958-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Meetings Attendance - NAM, 1960-1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Foremen, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- National Association of Manufacturers - Race, Civil Rights, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Strikes, Pickets, Oppositions, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Industrial Department Relations, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Industrial Kohler Reports, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NAM- News Articles, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Walter Judd, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Guranteed Annual Wage - NAM, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Unioning White Collar Votes, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Right to Work - Ira Latimer, 1939-1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Assorted NAM, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Pamphlets / Flyers, 1951-1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Speeches on Politics, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Strikes and Labor Legislator, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Southern Textile Industry, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- New Right News Coverage, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Jude Wanniski - Friedman, 1978-1979; 2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- NYT / Coverage OSHA / Enviornment WSJ, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Business Week 1970s (cont.), 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 1970s Articles, 1970-1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New Right 1970 News, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Christian Conservatives Reports, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Conservatism, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Labor, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Corporate IDs, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Stats, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Christianity Today 1970s (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Christianity Today 1960 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Chamber of Commerce 1970s, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Business Roundtable Notebook, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Irving Shapiro, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Business Roundtable, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- McCoy Papers, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Coors Articles, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- 1970s - Business Press and Ideology, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Business News Coverage, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Amway Articles, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Business in Politics, 1972-2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Charles Walker Roster, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 1970s Business and Politics Articles, 1964-1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 1970s Business and Politics Articles, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Sophia Lee RTW Essays, 2011; undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- NRWC - Group Research Report, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- William F. Knowland Journal and Papers, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Ben Peery Letter, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- NRTWC Newsletters, 1955-1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- More NRTWC Newsletters, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Manion - Gold Water Movement, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Manion - Goldwater, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Knowland Fundraising Letters, 1958-2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Clarence Manion Collection Letters about Goldwater, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Clarence Manion Collection Letters on Goldwater, the book, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Manion pre-1960 Political, 1954-1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Manion Radio Station, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Business and Political News Coverage, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- The Negro and His Right to Work, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Knowland Articles, 1945-1958 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Newspaper Articles on Politics, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- American Economic Foundation (AEC) - JEC (1, 2), 1958-1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Jasper Elliot Crane (JEC) Papers, Biography, 1938-1948 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Grae / Miller, Early Crane, 1938-1946 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Foundation for Economic Education (FEE) Fundraising Sources, 1948-1952 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Mullendore Papers, 1938-1955 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- FEE Pre-Ideology, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Mont Pelerin Society (MPS) - JEC (52, 53), 1945-1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- FEE - JEC, 1949-1960 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Jasper Crane Papers, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Rusher (?) Chile, 1975-1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- War 135, 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- War Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- War News Articles, 1958-1967 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- War Fundraising Contributors, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- William Rusher Papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
- War - American Conservative Union Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Stanley Hosbeck (ACU), undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Rusher Correspondence (COCA, CNP, etc), 1970-1975 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Wishnoff: Dissertation on Race, Public Housing, etc., 2005 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- Gregory Eow Dissertation, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
- Doug Soutar Material (Labor Law Study Group), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Douglas Soutar, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Federal Document Finding Aids, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Industrial Relations and other Academic Articles on Labor, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Fortune Articles Currently in Use, 1952-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- WSJ 1980 Campaign (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Big Business Day 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Reagan, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- American Conservative Union Papers, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Ford (articles) (Eduardo), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Powell Memo, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Powell Pages / Powell Memo, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Billy Graham Center Archives, 1961-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Democrats Recent Articles, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Contemporary Reference, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Emails, Printed Images, etc., 2008 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- ACU Papers, 1978-2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Rent Articles of Use, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- NAM 1970s, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Invisible Hands (Book), 2009 (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
- Race (Journal Articles, Newspaper clippings), 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
- Article for George, 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
- Ideology Conflict in American Ultraconservatism, 1945-1960, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Goddess of the Market: Ayn Rand and the American Right Disseration, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
- Invisible Hands with Annotations (Incomplete), undated (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
- Waterhouse Dissertation, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Jeff Decker, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- James Gross Papers and other Articles, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Nicole Hemmer, Manion, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Decker, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Ellie Shermer, West, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Eduardo Canedo, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- David Anderson Dissertation, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Companies, 2001; undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- National Association of Manufacturers, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Chamber of Commerce, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Hoover Institution, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Hugh Joseph Beard, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- William Miller, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Baroody, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Economics Articles, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Bethany Moreton, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Elizabeth Blackmar, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Alice O'Conner, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Bethany Moreton - Chapter 4, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Matt Lassiter, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Julia Ott, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Julia Ott Articles, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
- "God's Against Man: Carl McIntire ...", undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Bryan Thrift Dissertation, undated (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
- Lewis Brown 1930s, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Baltakis Dissertation, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Roger Milliken, 1956-2005 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Eisenhower, 1950s, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Papers of William J. Baroody, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Group Research Files, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
- National Review 1950s, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- AEA - 1950, 1949-1958 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Schwartz, Stacy, 1955-2007 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- AEA - GRA, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Roy Dudman Papers, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Dudman Archives, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- GRA 1960s Reports on Right Wing Finances, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- File Notes and Maps, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- AEI - Baroody 1970s, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- AEI / Baroody 1970s, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Rusher / Baroody Finding Aids, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- AEI / Baroody 1950s/60s, 1958-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- AEI / Baroody 1950s-60s, 1954-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- AEI / Baroody 1950s/60s, 1954-1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Bob Jones Unprocessed, 1962-2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Bob Jones Unprocessed, 1978-1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Bob Jones Unprocessed, 1968-2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Hazlitt - FEE, David Good(ing) - Fee, NICB - FEE, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Jasper Crane - FEE - Read, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Mullendore and FEE, 1945-1954 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- FEE Meetings, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Reader's Digest Ads BR, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Ayn Rand - FEE - James Beard, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Mirowski - Van Horn - Society Essay, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- GRA Files, 1961-2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Other Selections for Hayek Papers, 1945-1952 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Hayek Publication History - Reviews - Mirowski / VH, 1944-2006 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Mises - Hayek Letters, 1943-1960 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Jasper Crane Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- FEE - Hayek, 1947-1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Fritz Madslap and Bierely Hoover Institution, Hayek Papers, 1958-1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- William Grede FH Papers Hoover, 1954-1958 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Volker Related Articles (cites), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Friedman - Hayek Correspondence, 1947-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Hayek - Volker/Earhurt, 1945-1948 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- MPS, 1949-1957 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- 1947 (illegible) Refrin Papers, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 27-28)
- Local 833 UAW, 1952-1959 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Local 833 UAW, 1955-1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Manion - Kohler, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Sterling Morton / (illegible) Correspondence, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Manion 1964 Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Walter Reutr Collection, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Kohler Articles, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Robert Burkart Collection, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Kohler - NAM, 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Kohler UAW Region 106, 1954-1957 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Kohler Strike, 1954-1966 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- General Electric Publications, 1948-1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Article from Cornell, 1956; undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Kannenberg Dissertation, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Lyndon B. Johnson Papers, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 1960s Goldwater Coverage, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Barry Goldwater Archives, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Barry Goldwater, 1959-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Barry Goldwater, Miscellaneous, 1964-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Barry Goldwater Archives, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Denison Kitchel Papers, 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Denison Kitchel, 1956-1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Stephen Shadegy Papers, 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Free Society Association 1, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Free Society Association 2, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Regnery, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- 70s (illegible), GRA Studies, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Business Week: Death of Equities, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Clotworthy Papers, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- White, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Data on Strikes / Copper Crucible, 2008; undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Medicare Opponents, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Christian Right and Business, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Business / Clergy and Community, 1943-1959 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
- NAM Articles and Materials, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- NAM (illegible) Materials, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Management Rights, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- National Caterers, 1956-1959 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Hutchinson's Resignation from NAM, 1947-1951 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Hutchinson - NAM Correspondence, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Chad Pearson, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Chad Pearson, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Decker Dissertation, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
- Angus Bergin, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- James Morton Turner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Jeff Cowie, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Greta Krippner, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Robert Self, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Jacquelyn Hall, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Todd Holmes, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Industry-wide Bargaining, Arbitration (NAM, early 1940s), 1939-1945 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Sophie's Thesis, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Race, Feminist, and Business Politics Research, 1981-2006 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Nicole Hemmer, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
- Anti-Union, 1960-2005 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Unions, 2006; undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Fortune 500 Companies, 1955-1980 (Box 8, Folder 19-20)
- Bentley Historical Finding Aids / Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- NAM - Stafferman(?) Antiunion Materials, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- NAM and NLRB, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Hutchinson - Taft Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Jennifer Burns, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Labor Stuff, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Labor, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- COPE - NAM, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Conference Letters, proceedings, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Women, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Warner / Swasey, 1949-1956 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- NAM - Social Security, 1946-1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- NAM Business Philosophy Speeches, 1956-1960 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Unemployment, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- NAM Right to Work, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Open Shop, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Center for Union Power, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- NAM, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- ALane / The Great Utopia (Working Title), Draft of Manuscript, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
- Alane, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Dissertation Copy, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Dissertation Copy, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Dissertation Copy, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Dissertation Copy, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Ira Latimer, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Right to Work - Ira Latimer Collection, 1956-1964 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- AC Stevens Oral History, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- More Boulwarism, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- More Boulwarism, 1960-1966 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- General Electric, 1951-1960 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- 1960 Strike (Box 9, Folder 21)
- General Electric / Boulwarism, 1951-1960 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- General Election Strike and Memos, 1954-1960 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- General Electric Employee Relations Newsletters, 1949-1958 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- GE Corp Pamphlets, 1952-1961 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- GE Corp. Comm. Materials, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- IUE 301 Archives / History, 1967; undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Local 301 IUE, 1954-1960 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Press Coverage of Boulware / GE / General, 1946-1954 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Boulware 4/08 Visit, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Boulware Finding Aid, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- GE Schenctady News, 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- UE - Boulware, 1975-1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Cordiner Correspndence, 1958-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)